<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changelogs>
    <changelog>
        <element>mod_tflearnpath</element>
        <type>module</type>
        <version>1.4</version>

        <addition>
            <item>Added French language strings.</item>
            <item>Added a configuration field in the manifest file to choose the correct menu item for the paths view.</item>
        </addition>

        <change>
            <item>Updated the template file to force the selected menu item ID for paths view links.</item>
        </change>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>mod_tflearnpath</element>
        <type>module</type>
        <version>1.3</version>

        <fix>
            <item>Implemented AbstractModuleDispatcher logic for the dispatcher.</item>
            <item>Added logic to exit early inside the dispatcher when no course display is needed instead of throwing enqueueMessage.</item>
            <item>Removed the check inside the tmpl file for course display as this is now handled by the dispatcher.</item>
            <item>Fixed the helper function method call to remove unused $params variable.</item>
            <item>Changed the script file to use enqueueMessage instead of echo text.</item>
            <item>Standardized the manifest file and corrected duplicate copyright tags.</item>
            <item>Corrected the package name to TF Learn Path Module.</item>
        </fix>

        <change>
            <item><![CDATA[Moved <pre>$params->get</pre> calls inside the template file instead of the dispatcher.]]></item>
            <item><![CDATA[Moved <pre>params->get</pre> calls to the top of the tmpl file for clarity.]]></item>
            <item>Changed namespace to Naftee\Module\Tflearnpath\Site\Dispatcher.</item>
            <item>Changed namespace to Naftee\Module\Tflearnpath\Site\Helper.</item>
            <item>Updated namespaces in the service provider and manifest file.</item>
            <item>Added Tech Fry copyright information to the manifest.</item>
            <item>Added module-specific language strings and removed duplicated COM_TFLEARN module language strings.</item>
            <item>Removed author URL from the manifest.</item>
            <item>Updated blocks to version 1.3.</item>
            <item>Changed license to GPLv3.</item>
            <item>Updated sites configuration for Joomla! 5 and 6 support.</item>
        </change>

        <note>
            <item>Simplified the target platform configuration for Joomla! update sites.</item>
        </note>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>mod_tflearnpath</element>
        <type>module</type>
        <version>1.2</version>

        <fix>
            <item>Fixed helper file lesson retrieval so that all modules are displayed correctly.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>mod_tflearnpath</element>
        <type>module</type>
        <version>1.1</version>

        <fix>
            <item>Updated the helper file for compatibility with TF Learn 2.5.x and TF Library 2.9.x.</item>
        </fix>

        <change>
            <item>Blocked installation on Joomla! 4 because TF Learn versions after 2.4.4 are incompatible with Joomla! 4.</item>
        </change>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>mod_tflearnpath</element>
        <type>module</type>
        <version>1.0</version>

        <addition>
            <item>Initial release.</item>
        </addition>
    </changelog>
</changelogs>